<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Content tagged as &#39;Academic&#39; on Jose Emilio Labra Gayo</title>
    <link>http://labra.github.io/tags/academic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Content tagged as &#39;Academic&#39; on Jose Emilio Labra Gayo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Jose Emilio Labra Gayo</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/academic/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Home page</title>
      <link>http://labra.github.io/post/homepage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 10:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://labra.github.io/post/homepage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These days, in my spare time while on vacation, I decided to rewrite my home page.
 The task was not easy as I was doing it in a hotel in Lanzarote, without internet connection in my room,
 and using &lt;a href=&#34;http://gohugo.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;, a website framework, that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t used before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, Hugo seems quite intuitive and is very fast to compile and run, so it is funny for trial-and-error.
Also, there is a very nice &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gcushen/hugo-academic&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Academic theme&lt;/a&gt; which facilitated
the quick creation of the fist draft.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once I did the first draft and started to add content,
 I noticed that I had a long list of publications that required
 some extra-information like the journal, year or authors, so I had
 to customize the academic theme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to browse Hugo documentation while being online, I found useful &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/hamoid/long-hugo-doc&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;this project&lt;/a&gt;,
 which generated all Hugo documentation in a single HTML page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems that the customization can be easily done by replacing
 the pages that are in the themes folder by the equivalent ones in the root folder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had to change the pages:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;layouts/widgets/publication&lt;/code&gt;: declares how to visualize publications in the home page. I added a link at the end to show all publications.
I had also added some code to add filtering by tags, but the result is not nice, so I commented it. It seems that commenting code in HTML in Hugo requires to remove the &lt;code&gt;{{&lt;/code&gt; in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;layouts/partials/publication_li_simple.html&lt;/code&gt;: defines how to visualize a single publication (I added there the authors, publication and year)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;layouts/section/publication.html&lt;/code&gt;: declares how to filter publications by type and repeats the previous code. It would be better to use a partial, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to break things from the academic theme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also managed to integrate Travis with github so when I push some changes to github, it automatically deploys the content via Travis.
 Notice that there are 2 branches, the &lt;code&gt;source&lt;/code&gt; branch contains the source code, and the &lt;code&gt;master&lt;/code&gt; branch contains the result (in Hugo, the result is by default created in the folder &lt;code&gt;/public&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The source code is located &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/labra/labra.github.io&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and
 the resulting web page is &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.di.uniovi.es/~labra&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First post</title>
      <link>http://labra.github.io/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://labra.github.io/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the first post included in my home page.
I already have a &lt;a href=&#34;http://jelabra.blogspot.com.es/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;personal blog&lt;/a&gt;,
so I am not sure if I will really use this place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, who knows&amp;hellip;it seems quite easy to create posts here using
the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gcushen/hugo-academic&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Academic theme&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
